newenglandfilm.com 2006-06-15

# Privacy Policy at NewEnglandFilm.com

You are here: Home > About Us >   

**NewEnglandFilm.com Privacy Statement**

NewEnglandFilm.com, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: [http://www.nefilm.com](http://www.nefilm.com/) 

**User Information**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information.

Our site's **industry directory** form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and e-mail address). A user's contact information then becomes publicly listed on the web site as part of their listing.  Users may choose to only list an email, a phone or an address -- depending on how they wish to be contacted by other NewEnglandFilm.com users.

Similarly, when users choose to list a **classified ad** , they must list either their name or company and some form of contact information.  

**However, if someone is not listed on our site, that person's contact or personal information is never distributed to anyone.**

Users have the option to join the NewEnglandFilm monthly email update. This is a private and voluntary email list which users may opt-out of at any time using the instructions below.

Our site uses an order form for buyers to purchase products and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their e-mail address, mailing address) and financial information (like their credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. Please note that upon a purchase, the buyer's name, address and phone number is passed along to the seller so that the seller can ship the purchase. Sellers have an agreement with NewEnglandFilm.com to use this personal information only for order shipment and never for any other purpose. Financial information that is collected is only used to check the users' qualifications and bill the user for products and services.

Our online surveys and contests ask visitors for contact information (like their e-mail address) and demographic information (like their buying habits). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor only if they are the contest winner. Demographic and profile data collected through these surveys and contests are used for statistical purposes only and are not associated with individuals. As part of all surveys and contests, users may choose to join our email list or not to join.

**Sites We Link To**

This site contains links to other sites. NewEnglandFilm.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

You automatically enter our secure server when you click to "finalize" your order. Here, your personal and credit card information is protected with Netscape's SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption technology. SSL is the current standard for Internet commerce. NewEnglandFilm.com is committed to our customers' security, and will continue to offer the highest levels of protection for your credit card transactions.

NewEnglandFilm.com takes great measures to maintain the security of users' personal information. Only authorized employees are granted access to users' information and all information is password-protected. These few employees are authorized because it is integral to their job description. All NewEnglandFilm.com's employees are made aware of the company's privacy and security policies on hire.

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

To unsubscribe from our monthly email, send email to [monthly-update@newenglandfilm.com](mailto:monthly-update@newenglandfilm.com) with only the word "unsubscribe" in the BODY of your email message.  If you have any problems, contact us. 

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. Contact us with corrections.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

NewEnglandFilm.com, Inc.  
PO Box 391620  
Cambridge, MA 02139
